Finding Aid for Law School (University of Michigan) law lectures 1881-1919
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Thompson, Bradley Martin
  - Mortgages 1899 (Box 8)
  - Mortgages 1902 (Box 3)
  - Mortgages 1904 (Box 7)
  - Real estate law (Box 4)
  - Real estate law 1892 (Box 1)
  - Real estate law 1892 (Box 5)
  - Real estate law 1892 (Box 7)
  - Real estate law 1892 (Box 12)
  - Real estate law 1892 (Box 13)
  - Real estate law 1894 (Box 5)
  - Real estate law 1894 (Box 6)
  - Real estate law 1894 (Box 6)
  - Real estate law 1894 (Box 7)
  - Real property (Box 1)
  - Real property 1895 (Box 11)
  - Real property 1895 (Box 12)
  - Real property 1896 (Box 5)
  - Real property 1899 (Box 8)
  - Real property 1900 (Box 8)
  - Real property 1901 (Box 3)
  - Real property 1903 (Box 2)
  - Suretyship and mortgage (Box 10)
  - Suretyship and mortgages 1900 (Box 2)
  - Torts 1897 (Box 10)
  - Torts 1899 (Box 9)
  - Torts 1900 (Box 3)
  - Torts 1902 (Box 2)
  - Torts 1902 (Box 10)
  - Trial by ordeal (Box 5)
- Vaughan, Victor Clarence
  - Medical jurisprudence 1902 (Box 3)
- Walker, Albert Henry
  - Patent law 1898 (Box 11)
  - Patent law 1899 (Box 8)
- Walker, Charles Irish
  - Contracts 1881 (Box 1)
- Wells, William Palmer
  - Parliamentary law (Box 1)
  - Agency 1891 (Box 4)
  - Agency 1891 (Box 12)
  - Bills of exchange and promissory notes 1881 (Box 1)
  - Partnership (Box 10)
  - Partnership 1891 (Box 4)
  - Partnership 1891 (Box 12)
- Wilgus, Horace Lafayette
  - Citizenship of corporations 1898 (Box 8)
  - Corporations (Box 10)
  - Law of corporations (Box 4)
  - Modern action at law 1919 (Box 10)
  - Outline of Cooley's Torts (Box 10)
  - Outline of Cooley's Torts (Box 10)
  - Synopsis of torts (Box 9)
- Wilson, Leroy Allen
  - Outline of Greenleaf (Box 8)
  - Outline of Stephen's Pleading (Box 8)